<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dawg &amp; Hen</title>
    <link>https://dawghen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dawg &amp; Hen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:10:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dawghen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dec 21, NBA highlights</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-21-nba-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-21-nba-highlights/</guid>
      <description>KAT had a good game but couldn&amp;#39;t steer T-wolves to victory.      LeBron James gave a great performance with the absence of AD but couldn&amp;#39;t steer the team to victory.        Brandon Ingram steered a team to victory against the Blazers.      No Doncic, No Porzingis, No Tim Hardaway Jr., No Clever, yet Brunson is dealing against the T-wolves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 20, NBA highlights</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-20-nba-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 15:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-20-nba-highlights/</guid>
      <description>Kenrich Williams is a worth watching player.      SGA continues amazing clutch performances.      Healthy Joel Embiid is unstoppable.      Stephen Curry gave a great performance on the 4th quarter after extra mid-game rest.      Tyrese Haliburton, the sophomore of the King, keeps strong with the absence of Fox.      Dejounte Murray gave a great performance against the Clippers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 19, NBA highlights</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-19-nba-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 23:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-19-nba-highlights/</guid>
      <description>The Blazers beat the Grizzlies, the hottest team in the league right now. The Norm&amp;#39;s clutch performance shone.      LaVine was out but DeRozan saved the Bulls.      Jaylen Nowell backed up Anthony Edwards. He showed good shot-creating skill and a spot-up 3 point jumper.      Robert Covington has been great as a sixth man of the Blazers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 16, NBA highlights</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-16-nba-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 20:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-16-nba-highlights/</guid>
      <description>   There&amp;#39;s a rumor 5 teams pursue Caris LeVert of the Pacers. This could be a good showcase against the Pistons.      No Irving. No Harden. No Harris. The slim reaper is dealing.      Cade Cunningham continues improved performance. The top drafted prospect rising   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 15, NBA highlights</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-15-nba-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-15-nba-highlights/</guid>
      <description>Russ got near triple-double. He helped the team to win the game and assisted the winning shot by Reaves in overtime.
 Russell Westbrook game and season stats     Antman recorded the franchise-high 3 points shot made. All shots including missed (he barely missed today though ) and one assist
  Jrue Holiday had a great game against the Pacers without Giannis
  Gabe Vincent made a couple of big shots in the game against the 76ers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 14, NBA highlights</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-14-nba-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 20:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/dec-14-nba-highlights/</guid>
      <description>  Scottie Barnes&#39; great performance against the Brooklyn Nets.
 Short profile for SB4      Gary Trent Jr. made an effort for the win vs Nets     Kessler Edwards, the rookie of the Nets, had a career-high game against the Raptors and assisted the team to win the game.
 Savior    Precious   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OffRtg for a small line-up with the center, Lebron James</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/offrtg-for-a-small-line-up-with-the-center-lebron-james/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 16:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/12/offrtg-for-a-small-line-up-with-the-center-lebron-james/</guid>
      <description>When the Clippers did beat the Lakers&#39; small line-up put LeBron James at the center postion in the 4th quarter. Many including LeBron himself criticized the bad defense
LeBron says he knew he wouldn&amp;#39;t have what he needed tonight after four straight days off. Emphasized that in the lineup with him and Melo at the 4 and 5, he was &amp;quot;pretty shitty&amp;quot; on the defensive end. But says that he was just grateful to be out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA drive leaders</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/11/nba-drive-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/11/nba-drive-leaders/</guid>
      <description>NBA players with Drives per game &amp;gt; 12. T.J. McConnell made elite figures with 26 MP. FGM, AST%, FG% all good. Brogdon&amp;rsquo;s also impressive
Ja Morant is the FGM leader for drives, Josh Giddey is the only rookie for the conditions, drives per game &amp;gt; 12.
NBA players with Drives per game &amp;gt; 12. T.J. McConnell made elite figures with 26 MP. FGM, AST%, FG% all good. Brogdon&amp;#39;s also impressive #McConnell #NBAstats pic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Links</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/_draft/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/_draft/links/</guid>
      <description>Inpredictable: WPA and others, NBA
https://www.coachesclipboard.net/BasketballOffenses.html
wording https://www.canishoopus.com/2021/10/1/22697622/a-sampling-of-what-the-timberwolves-offense-could-evolve-into-chris-finch-karl-anthony-towns
#deep https://github.com/neeilan/DeepPlayByPlay
https://github.com/Basket-Analytics/BasketTracking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Gavin Lux couldn&#39;t accept the fly-out </title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/10/why-gavin-lux-couldnt-accept-the-fly-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/10/why-gavin-lux-couldnt-accept-the-fly-out/</guid>
      <description>We put the Statcast info on every pitch and hit. It contains more informations than our intuition sometimes. The estimated batting average, estimated slugging from the exit velocity and the launch angle shows Gavin&amp;rsquo;s hit could have been a homer or an extra base hit at least. Gavin must have felt it&amp;rsquo;d be a bif fly after he hit it hard.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aroldis Chapman&#39;s New Money Pitch</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/05/aroldis-chapmans-new-money-pitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 14:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/2021/05/aroldis-chapmans-new-money-pitch/</guid>
      <description>Aroldis Chapman, the elite closer of the New York Yankees is well-known as 100 mph fastball and a hard slider. He has been seeking his 3rd pitch type and finally seems to succeed in adding a new pitch type. He threw the splitters 3 times (out of 199 ) last season. From the animated pics, Chapman&amp;rsquo;s usage of the splitters are over 10% this season. (Currently, 13.3%)
This 100 mph closer is using the new pitch as a winning shot already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About The Channel</title>
      <link>https://dawghen.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dawghen.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Dawg&amp;amp;Hen, or D&amp;amp;H try to add more joy to various topics with a visual impact. For example, we start with normal baseball highlight clips which the official MLB highlight missed out. And eventually, we’d include pitch-info, sabermetrics, and so on, whatever if it can make more fun in the ballgame or provide baseball fans food for thought.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
